(Penny:)- How do I get the sword?
- Have you been to the Temple of Mitra?
- Is that the place on the hill with the priest?
- No, it's...
Oh, for God's sakes, give me.
(Penny:)Thank you. I really appreciate this.
You have to learn to do these things.
Don't patronize me. Just get the sword.
(Howard:)What the frak?
(Leonard:)Beats me.
They were playing all last night too.
(Raj:)It's like some kind
of weird comic-book crossover.
(Howard:)Like if Hulk
were dating Peppermint Patty.
(Raj:)I always thought Peppermint Patty
was a lesbian.
(Leonard:)No, that's Marcie.
(Leonard:)Peppermint Patty's just athletic.
(Sheldon:)There you go, one enchanted sword.
All right, give me, give me.
I wanna kill the guard captain.
(Sheldon:)That girl needs to get a life.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]